Speaking from experience, you're going to feel tempted to buy something today.
The sales, the sales, the sales, the seals.
Don't.
And yes, black businesses, I mean you too.
Because our Black Friday should not be on a Black Friday.
We should have our own Black Friday and it should happen on a day of blackness.
It should be either on the day before or after Martin Luther King's birthday is observed.
It could be during Black History Month.
It could be on Juneteenth.
Look at that.
If we're not going to go to work, let's spend our money with us.
There's nothing to buy today that you can't buy tomorrow.
And ultimately whatever they're selling you, you probably actually already have.
And you don't need another one.
So let's try our best.
Let's see how we do.
Let's see how we do not behaving like we've done in the past knowing what we know now.
I wish you luck once more into the breach.
Now this is the part of the video where I usually sell you something.
You know, because I got things.
I'm a merchant.
But to show you that I mean what I mean about today, I don't even want you to buy nothing from me today.
How about that?
Just subscribe to my YouTube, Amanda Seals TV.
Let's see.